{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Theater Wiring Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/39783/":{"taskOID":39783,"originalTaskOID":39783,"setID":315,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6425,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8775,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New install - existing space","answerDisplayText":"New install - existing space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8776,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel - re-wire everything","answerDisplayText":"Remodel - re-wire everything","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8777,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New install - addition or new construction","answerDisplayText":"New install - addition or new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8778,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remodel - re-wire a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Remodel - re-wire a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6426,"questionDisplayText":"Type of wiring","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of wiring do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8779,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cable or other video wiring","answerDisplayText":"Cable or other video wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8780,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Satellite TV wiring","answerDisplayText":"Satellite TV wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8781,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home Theater component wiring","answerDisplayText":"Home Theater component wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8782,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"High-end Home Theater or Automation wiring","answerDisplayText":"High-end Home Theater or Automation wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8783,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Modem or internet wiring","answerDisplayText":"Modem or internet wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8784,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6427,"questionDisplayText":"Wall and ceiling access","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please describe the wall and ceiling access.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8785,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls must be left intact","answerDisplayText":"Walls must be left intact","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8786,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial wall access","answerDisplayText":"Partial wall access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8787,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic or below floor access","answerDisplayText":"Attic or below floor access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8788,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"All walls will be exposed","answerDisplayText":"All walls will be exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":10020,"questionDisplayText":"Request is for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a commercial location?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a commercial location?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6425,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8775,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New install - existing space","answerDisplayText":"New install - existing space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8776,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel - re-wire everything","answerDisplayText":"Remodel - re-wire everything","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8777,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New install - addition or new construction","answerDisplayText":"New install - addition or new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8778,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remodel - re-wire a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Remodel - re-wire a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8775,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New install - existing space","answerDisplayText":"New install - existing space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8776,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel - re-wire everything","answerDisplayText":"Remodel - re-wire everything","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8777,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New install - addition or new construction","answerDisplayText":"New install - addition or new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8778,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remodel - re-wire a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Remodel - re-wire a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6426,"questionDisplayText":"Type of wiring","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of wiring do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8779,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cable or other video wiring","answerDisplayText":"Cable or other video wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8780,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Satellite TV wiring","answerDisplayText":"Satellite TV wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8781,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home Theater component wiring","answerDisplayText":"Home Theater component wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8782,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"High-end Home Theater or Automation wiring","answerDisplayText":"High-end Home Theater or Automation wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8783,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Modem or internet wiring","answerDisplayText":"Modem or internet wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8784,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8779,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cable or other video wiring","answerDisplayText":"Cable or other video wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8780,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Satellite TV wiring","answerDisplayText":"Satellite TV wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8781,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home Theater component wiring","answerDisplayText":"Home Theater component wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8782,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"High-end Home Theater or Automation wiring","answerDisplayText":"High-end Home Theater or Automation wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8783,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Modem or internet wiring","answerDisplayText":"Modem or internet wiring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8784,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6427,"questionDisplayText":"Wall and ceiling access","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please describe the wall and ceiling access.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8785,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls must be left intact","answerDisplayText":"Walls must be left intact","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8786,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial wall access","answerDisplayText":"Partial wall access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8787,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic or below floor access","answerDisplayText":"Attic or below floor access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8788,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"All walls will be exposed","answerDisplayText":"All walls will be exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8785,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls must be left intact","answerDisplayText":"Walls must be left intact","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8786,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial wall access","answerDisplayText":"Partial wall access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8787,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic or below floor access","answerDisplayText":"Attic or below floor access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8788,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"All walls will be exposed","answerDisplayText":"All walls will be exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":10020,"questionDisplayText":"Request is for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a commercial location?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a commercial location?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/39783/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":39783,"taskName":"Home Theater Wiring - Install, Repair or Conceal","taskDescription":"Install, Repair, or Conceal Home Theater Wiring","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Theater Wiring Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":129,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"home theatre entertainment AV audio","textMessagingName":"Home Theater Wiring","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes the Installation, Repair or Concealment of all Home Theater Wiring.  This includes Cable, Modem, Network and other Audio or Video wiring.  This person would run lines on the surface or in walls, install jacks \u0026 extend connections and plug in components.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes audio and video wiring for Home Theater Systems","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install, Repair, or Conceal Home Theater Wiring.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Home Theater Wiring Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Hide Wires, Install or Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":6,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Install, Repair, or Conceal Home Theater Wiring","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Home Theater Wiring - Install, Repair or Conceal","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Theater Wiring Project","urlName":"Home-Theater-Wiring-Install-Repair-or-Conceal","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Theater Wiring Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Hide Wires","searchKeywords":"home,theatre,entertainment,AV,audio","emcCategoryOid":-12006,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":315,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}